openthemagazine.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Open The Magazine

At Open we take your privacy seriously. Open is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**What this policy covers**  
This policy covers how Open treats personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your use of Open publications, products and other related services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address , phone number etc. and that is not otherwise publicly available.  
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Open does not own or control or to people that Open does not employ or manage.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
**General**  
Open may collect personal information when you register with Open, when you use Open publications, products or services, when you visit Open pages or the pages of certain Open business partners. Open may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register Open may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, PIN/ZIP code, employment/occupation details, industry and personal interests. For some products and services Open might also ask for your address, address proof document, PAN number, and information about your assets. When you register with Open and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Open collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your reading of our publications, use of products and services that we offer.

Open may use information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for publications, products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing and disclosure**  
Open does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Open under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Open communicate with you about offers from Open and our business partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Open terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if Open is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Open will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Open does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

Editing Your Account Information and Preferences  
You can edit your Open Account information including your preferences at any time.

New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Open service, such as service announcements, administrative messages, promotional material and the Open Newsletter, that may be considered a part of your Open account.

**Confidentiality and Security**  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Open may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Open account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Jurisdiction**  
All disputes are subject to the laws of India and exclusive jurisdiction of the competent Courts and Forums in Calcutta only.

**Questions/ Suggestions**  
For any questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or contact us at:

Open Media Network Private Limited, 33 Jessore Road, Dum Dum, Kolkata 700028

(Effective from 29 April, 2009)
